你看到拉杰刚才发的状态了吗
Aw, man, did you see this post from Raj?
发什么了  又一部他跟他的狗
What? Is it another video of him and his dog
"小姐与流浪汉式"地共吃面条影片吗
Lady-and-the-Tramping some spaghetti?
迪士尼卡通电影经典段落
片中两条狗从一条面条的两端慢慢吃到亲嘴
不是  他住不起那个公寓了
No. He can't afford his apartment,
在问有没有人知道哪里有便宜的住处
and he's asking if anyone knows of a cheap place to live.
我想回"印度"  但感觉太贱了
I want to say "India," but it seems mean.
什么事那么好笑
What's so funny?
拉杰在找便宜的地方住
Raj is looking for a cheap place to live,
我回了"印度"
and I wrote "India."
别回这个  给人家点支持
Don't post that; be supportive.
那你怎么不支持一下我的这些搞笑段子
Maybe you should be supportive of my hilarious jokes.
行  那我们该怎么做
Fine, what should we do?
我们这么聪明  肯定能想出办法
We're smart. I'm sure we can think of something.
你想让他住我们这里吗
You want to let him live here?
我们绝对比那聪明多了
Oh, we're smarter than that.
我知道我们的公寓很小
I know our apartment's small,
但挤一挤还是能挤出位子吧
but I think we can make room.
谢尔顿  不行
No, Sheldon.
不许买真人大小的蜘蛛侠人像
We are not getting a life-size Spider-Man statue.
家里的确还有谢尔顿的旧房间
We do have Sheldon's old room.
如果他真的需要落脚处
If he really needs a place to stay,
我们可以让给他住
I guess we should offer it to him.
你真是个好兄弟
You're a good friend.
那如果我先等一会儿并期待
Am I still a good friend if I wait and hope
霍华德先邀他去住他家  还算好兄弟吗
that Howard offers him a place to live first?
你还是个更棒的老公
You're an even better husband.
我知道如果是换作我落魄
I know if the roles were reversed,
他一定会伸出援手
he would do it for me.
那他睡哪啊
Where would he stay?
我们已经收留斯图尔特了
We already have Stuart.
我们可以在车库里腾出位子啊
Well, we can make some space in the garage.
给他弄个小床
Maybe put a cot out there,
再弄台小暖气  或者一台电热炉
get him a space heater, maybe a hot plate.
听起来好惨啊
That sounds awful.
希望他也会这么觉得
Let's hope he thinks so, too.
我再说一次
For the last time,
绿巨人  蝙蝠侠  任何真人大小人像都不行
no Hulk, no Batman, no life-size statues.
我开始觉得其实
I'm starting to think you didn't mean it
你并不是真心想要布置一下家里
when you said you wanted to spruce up the place.
你好
Hello.
我与妮妮讨论了一下
Hey, uh, so we've been talking,
如果你需要地方住
and if you need a place to stay,
我们很乐意帮你收拾一下车库
we'd be happy to fix up the garage for you.
那就太棒了
That would be amazing!
我刚才真的就看着我的纸箱子
I was literally just looking at my moving boxes,
寻思着要挑哪个住进去了
trying to pick one to live in.
虽然条件不太理想
I know it's not ideal,
但好歹里面有很多空间放你的家具
but you'd have plenty of space for your furniture,
还有个很酷的按钮
and there's this cool button
能让你其中一面"墙"卷起来又放下去呢
that makes an entire wall go up and down.
真是太感谢你了
I cannot thank you enough.
能帮你我们也很高兴
It is our pleasure.
你能等我一下吗
Hey, can you hold on one sec?
你好
Hello?
兄弟  你还在找地方住吗
Hey, buddy, you still looking for a place to live?
是啊
Uh... yeah.
为什么这么问
Why do you ask?
我们这里有多一间空房间
You know, we have the extra bedroom,
如果你有需要  那就让你住吧
and if you need it, it's yours.
天啊  你们真是太大方了
Oh, my God, that's so generous!
小事一件不足挂齿
It's the least we can do.
我真的很感谢
I-I really appreciate it.
你能稍等我一下吗
Uh, can you hold on one second?
霍华德  所以我的浴室是怎么样
Hey, so, Howard, what's the bathroom situation gonna be?
外面有个水槽...
Well, there's a sink out there--
能帮你解决你一半的问题
that takes care of half your problems.
但是我能用楼下的浴室对吧
But I can use the downstairs bathroom, right?
行  我们不怎么用  跟你的独立卫浴差不多
Yeah. We barely use it, so it'll be like it's yours.
很好  很好
Cool, cool, yeah.
-那你再稍等我一下  -什么
- Yeah, hold on one second. - Wh...?
跟佩妮共用一个浴室是什么感觉
Hey, what's it like sharing a bathroom with Penny?
会不会到处都是她的头发
Is there hair everywhere?
她会不会偷用你的浴球
Does she use your loofah?
我没有浴球
I don't have a loofah.
好吧  如果我搬进去  你也不许用我的
Okay, well, if I move in, you can't use mine.
再等我一下
Hold on a second.
霍华德  车库里的无线网信号如何
Hey, Howard, uh, how's the Wi-Fi in the garage?
我也不知道
I don't know.
你为啥要问这么多问题啊
Why are you asking all these questions?
老实告诉你  莱纳德也在跟我通话
Well, to be honest, Leonard's on the other line,
他邀请我去住他家那间空房
and he offered me their spare bedroom.
太好啦  住他那儿吧
Great! Go live there.
可是你把住车库说得很有趣啊
But you made the garage sound so fun.
我只是不想你觉得住车库很惨
I just didn't want you to feel bad about it.
除非莱纳德的公寓也会有浣熊
Unless Leonard's apartment also has a raccoon
在冬夜里啃破墙壁爬进来  不然就去住吧
that chews its way in on cold nights, go there!
等一会儿
One second.
就差最后一步了
Okay, I think we're close.
你对我房里放个小冰箱有意见吗
How do you feel about a mini-fridge in my room?
兄弟  你还想不想住了
Hey, pal, you want to live here or not?
佩妮  住住住  麻烦您了
Oh, uh, hi, Penny. Yes, please.
佩妮  这张传单是给"住户"的
Uh, Penny, this circular is addressed to "Occupant,"
但是我们现在换着住
but with our apartment switch,
我弄不太清是给你还是给我的
it's unclear whether it's yours or mine.
是干嘛的传单
What's it for?
铺屋顶
Roofing.
那肯定是你的了
Yeah, it's yours.
好吧  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
"直接扔了吧"
"Just throw it out."
说到住户  根据我听到的消息
Speaking of occupants, I'm given to understand
拉杰会搬到我以前的房间
Raj will be moving into my old room.
是啊  暂住一阵
Yeah, for a little while.
那他的狗呢
What about his dog?
她会住在她的笼子里  问题不大
She'll be in her crate; it's not a big deal.
那我还算能接受吧
I suppose that's acceptable.
谢尔顿现在比较敢接近狗了
Well, Sheldon's getting a little better with dogs.
他这次还在迪士尼乐园跟布鲁托合照了呢
He even took a picture with Pluto at Disneyland.
如果真的狗也会送我胸章  那我也喜欢他们
If real dogs gave me buttons, I'd like them, too.
我觉得你们愿意
Well, I think it's very nice
帮忙朋友是一件很棒的事
that you're helping out our friend.
我倒觉得你也很棒  无论艾米给你什么药
I think it's nice that you're taking whatever medication
你都照单全吃
Amy's clearly giving you.
这话是什么意思
And what is that supposed to mean?
这就跟某个科学定律一样
Well, it's like that science thing.
有任何举动[作用]
For every action,
你都会有又大又烦人的反应[反作用]
you have a gigantic and annoying reaction.
真想不到我老婆美貌与智慧并存啊
Just when I thought you couldn't get any hotter.
如果你俩是暗示我会不爽
If you're implying that I'd have some problem
拉杰搬进我的房间  那你们就错了
with him moving into my room, you're wrong.
拉杰现在的财务状况十分困难
Raj is in a difficult financial situation,
我很高兴他能做出改变去改善它
and I'm glad that he's making changes to improve it.
药量不需要调整  你做得很好
Do not adjust the dosage. You nailed it.
别听他们胡说
Don't listen to them.
奇怪的是佩妮居然差点就说对了一个科学事实
What's weird is that Penny almost got a science fact right.
太不公平了  人们都觉得我会不爽
I mean, it's unfair; people just assume I'm going to be upset
拉杰搬进我的旧房间
by Raj moving into my old room.
可你确实是  不是吗
But you are, aren't you?
我不爽到极点
Oh, I'm outraged.
跟我说说  到底怎么回事
Talk to me. Tell me what's going on.
在我没认识莱纳德之前  我就住那个房间
Well, that's been my room since before I met Leonard,
现在却有别人要搬进去住
and now someone else is going to be living in it.
而那个别人还不是我
And that someone else is not me.
你也知道我对于不是我的"别人"作何感想
And you know how I feel about people who aren't me.
我知道那个房间里充满了回忆
There are a lot of memories wrapped up in that room.
对我来说也是
For me, too.
你第一次说爱我就是在那个房间
The first time you told me you loved me was in that room.
错
Wrong.
当时我们站在我房间外的走廊
We were standing outside my room in the hallway.
这就是我刚说到的爱
And there is the love of which I speak.
我知道这样很不理性
I realize it's irrational,
但拉杰的入住让我觉得自己被取代了
but with Raj moving in there, I'm feeling a bit replaced.
现在对他来说是困难时期
Well, this isn't an easy time for him.
他公寓没了  还欠了一屁股债
He's losing his apartment, he's in debt,
他可能正羞愧难当呢
he's probably humiliated.
是啊  可能
Yes, probably.
但在确定之前  我该怎么才能舒坦呢
But until we know for sure, how can I feel better?
你们谁还需要什么吗
Can I get anyone anything at all?
拉杰  你不用服务我们
Raj, you don't have to serve us.
这是我该做的  谢谢你们帮我搬我的家当上楼
It's the least I can do for helping me carry my stuff up.
真的没什么大不了的
It was really no problem.
对你来说当然啦  你只搬了一箱毛巾
Not for you, Box of Towels.
总而言之  谢谢你们
Anyway, thanks again.
瞧瞧
Hey, look at that.
你们有拉杰  我们有斯图尔特
You've got a Raj, we've got a Stuart.
或许我们该带他俩去公园
Maybe we should take them both to the park
让他们一起撒欢跑跑
and let them run around together.
我不知道  你那只看起来身上有虫子
I don't know. Yours looks like he has worms.
可以走了吗
You ready to go?
一切准备妥当
All set.
那是什么
What's that?
给拉杰的乔迁礼物
A housewarming gift for Raj.
最好不是一大堆假蛇突然从里面冒出来
Well, a bunch of fake snakes better not spring out of it,
因为那是一份超烂的纪念日礼物
'cause that was a lousy anniversary present.
绝对不会
It's nothing like that.
我考虑到拉杰现在的情况
I just, I thought about Raj's situation,
于是我改变了主意
and I had a change of heart.
而且关于你的礼物
You know, and regarding your gift,
是你自己说"给我惊喜"  而我的确"惊"到你了
you said "Surprise me," and, boy, did I.
时间刚刚好  食物都准备好了
Perfect timing. Food's ready.
等等  在开吃之前  我有一份小小的
Uh, wait-- before we eat, I have a little
"欢迎入住"礼物要给拉杰
"Welcome to the building" gift for Raj.
慢着  是不是会蹦出什么...
Wait, is anything gonna jump out...
不是  我问过了
No. I already asked.
谢谢  谢尔顿
Thank you, Sheldon.
是一本...空白的笔记本
It's a... blank notebook.
我曾在那个房间里想出过不少好点子
Well, I had some of my best ideas in that room,
我相信你也会的
and I'm sure you will, too.
他也未曾在那个房间里做过爱呢
He also never had sex in that room.
那是另一件值得期盼的事情啊
That's something else to look forward to.
这对我来说意义重大
This means a lot.
我知道现在对你来说是困难时期
Well, I know this is a difficult time for you.
你的公寓没了  还欠了一屁股债
Y-You're losing your apartment, you're in debt,
你可能...肯定羞愧难当吧
and you just-- you must be humiliated.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
哎呀  老天
Oh, good grief.
她真爱拘泥于细节  非得注明出处
She is such a stickler for citing sources.
那些都是艾米的原话
Those were Amy's words.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
我知道  我知道
I know, I know!
"哎呀  老天"是查理·布朗的原话  真是够了
"Good grief" was originally said by Charlie Brown, geez.
美国著名漫画《史努比》里的主人公
他犯错或是遇到难题时的口头禅
你说得对  我是羞愧难当
You're right, I am humiliated.
多谢当面指出来
Thanks for pointing it out.
你真是个混蛋
You're such a jerk.
你们能相信他居然这么说我吗
Can you believe this guy?
能
Yes.
我还以为会听到另一种答案呢
I-I thought that was gonna break the other way.
走吧  谢尔顿
Come on, Sheldon.
或许我们应该回自己公寓吃饭
Maybe we should just eat at our place.
好吧
Fine.
你占了我的房间
You took my room.
你还让我的朋友跟我翻脸
You turned my friends against me.
现在你开心啦
I hope you're happy.
我有什么值得开心的
What do I have to be happy about?
我的人生一团糟
My life's a wreck.
为什么他可以说出来  而我却不能
How come he can say it and I can't?
快走吧你
Just keep walking.
你好呀  谢尔顿
Hello, Sheldon.
真是意外之喜呀
What a pleasant surprise.
你好吗
How are you?
老实说  最近好多了
Honestly, I've been better.
你有时间吗
Do you have time?
莱纳德说你最近很忙
Leonard says you're very busy these days.
我这么说是因为他爱闲聊
Oh, I just say that because he prattles.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
我们的朋友拉杰搬进了我的旧房间
Well, our friend Raj moved into my old room,
这事导致我产生了很多负面情绪
and it's brought up a lot of negative feelings for me.
你觉得失去你的旧房间代表了什么
Well, what do you think the loss of your room represents?
贝弗利  你知道我十分敬重你
Beverly, you know I hold you in high esteem.
我们可以跳过你假装不知道答案的戏码
Can we skip the part where you pretend not to know the answer,
直接进入你告诉我答案的环节吗
and get to the part where you tell me the answer?
好的  但你不介意的话
Very well, but, uh, if you don't mind,
为了戏剧化效果  我还是要停顿一下
I'd still like to pause for effect.
现在嘛...
Now...
你最近和福勒博士同居了  对吧
You've recently moved in with Dr. Fowler, yes?
没错
I have.
显然你的旧房间代表了一个逃生出口
Clearly, your old room represents an escape hatch,
倘若失去了这出口  你就将被迫面对
and without it, you're forced to confront
和艾米永远生活
the terrifying reality of being trapped
在一起的可怕现实
in a relationship with Amy forever.
我从未想过这问题
I hadn't thought about that.
现在也别开始想
And don't start thinking about it now!
你好呀  艾米
Hello, Amy.
你的这种防御表现似乎也在暗示
Your defensiveness may indicate similar insecurities
你对于这份感情有同样的不安全感
about your relationship with Sheldon.
才不是这样的
That's not true!
她极具防御性地说
She said defensively.
这不是关于我和谢尔顿的问题
This isn't about me and Sheldon.
而是拉杰要搬去和莱纳德还有佩妮一起住
This is about Rajesh moving in with Leonard and Penny.
有点意思
Interesting.
他们发现自己需要再找一个室友了
They've found a need to take yet another roommate.
看来他们也在努力回避二人世界中的残酷现实呀
Seems they're avoiding some harsh realities themselves.
我真没想到
I had no idea
我们这些人的感情生活都是一团乱麻
all our relationships were such a disaster.
唉呀妈呀  你可真厉害
Boy, you're good.
道上的确都是这么传的
That is the word on the street, dear.
也许搬进来并不是个好主意
Maybe moving in was a bad idea.
我屁股还没坐热  就已经开始制造麻烦了
I haven't been here one day, I'm already causing problems.
这不是你的错  都怪谢尔顿
You didn't do anything. It's Sheldon.
"这不是你的错  都怪谢尔顿"
"You didn't do anything. It's Sheldon."
这句话太适合绣在靠垫上了
That'd make a nice needlepoint pillow.
放轻松  我们很欢迎你来住
So, relax. We're happy to have you.
多谢  不过我怎么知道
Thank you, but how do I know
你不是为了安慰我才这么说的呢
you're not saying that just to be nice?
你怎么花钱剪了个狗啃似的发型
Do you actually pay for that haircut?
现在我知道了
That'll do it.
拉杰  我欠你一个道歉
Hey, Raj, I owe you an apology.
你能给你那狗拴个绳子吗
Look, could you please put your dog on a leash?
谢尔顿  我这狗不咬人
Sheldon, she's fine.
那你把她抱紧了
Well, then at least hold her still
我好假装她是个动物标本
so I can pretend she's stuffed.
拉杰  我一时没控制住自己的情绪
Raj, I let my emotions get the best of me,
乱拿你来出气
and I unfairly took it out on you.
谢谢  谢谢你这么说
Thank you. I appreciate that.
不  功劳不在我身上
No, I can't take all the credit.
我和莱纳德的妈妈聊了聊  她开解了我
I spoke with Leonard's mother, and she made me feel better.
我不知道你和谁聊了  但会开解人的一定不是我妈
I don't know who you talked to, but that wasn't my mother.
贝弗利指出我在和艾米的恋爱关系中
Beverly pointed out that I'm experiencing insecurities
存在不安全感
in my relationship with Amy,
就像莱纳德和佩妮也存在同样的问题
in the same way that Leonard and Penny are in their relationship.
你在乱说什么呀  我们俩好着呢
What are you talking about? We're fine.
你俩好着的前提是有一个缓冲人同住
Yes, you're fine as long as you have a buffer
才能帮你们转移婚姻中出现的问题
living with you to distract from your marital problems.
从前我就是那个缓冲人
It used to be me.
现在轮到拉杰和他的攻击性毛毛球了
Now it's Raj and his attack Tribble.
总之  我很抱歉
Anyway, I'm sorry for everything.
顺带一提  如果他们吵架时你哇哇大哭
Oh, and FYI-- if you cry while they're fighting,
他们就会带你去麦当劳
they'll take you to McDonald's.
你好  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard.
你为什么说我们有婚姻问题呀
Why are you saying we have marital problems?
我们才没有婚姻问题呢
We don't have marital problems!
我懂了  那你是因为太过幸福美满才对我哇哇叫
I see. You must be yelling at me out of wedded bliss.
就因为我们收留朋友来住
Look, just because we took our friend in does not mean
并不代表我和佩妮害怕两人独处
that Penny and I are afraid to be alone.
没错  这次是特殊情况
Yeah, this is a special circumstance.
谢尔顿提到你也曾想让
Sheldon mentioned you tried to get your brother
你哥哥住到家里来
to live with you, as well.
是啊  有些情况就算发生两次
Yeah, well, a circumstance can happen twice
仍然可以算作特殊
and still be special.
你同意吗
Do you agree with that?
既然你这么指出来...
Well, now that you point it out...
你疯了吧
Are you kidding me?
我们好像真的一直在找新室友
We do seem to keep finding roommates.
你现在和她站一边了吗
Now you're taking her side?
亲爱的  我永远不会夹在你和莱纳德之间
Dear, I would never come between you and Leonard.
这是你们一加强连的室友的工作
That's for your parade of roommates to do.
霍华德
Howard?
Howard!
是我  是我呀
It's me! It's just me!
你跑到我们卧室来干嘛
What are you doing here?!
人家给你发了短信  可你没有回复
Well, I texted you, but you didn't respond.
莱纳德和佩妮在吵架...
Leonard and Penny were arguing...
本大爷在此  谁敢撒野
Not on my watch!
没事了  是拉杰
It's fine. It's just Raj.
我不介意你拿球棒敲死他  但我们没事
You can hit him with the bat, but it's fine.
如果我心跳停止了  请让我放弃治疗
And if my heart stops, just let me go.
抱歉了各位
I'm sorry, guys.
谢尔顿在生气  莱纳德和佩妮在吵架
Sheldon was upset, Leonard and Penny were fighting.
我只想待在一个不会造成别人问题的地方
I just wanted to go someplace where I wasn't causing problems.
我要再说一次
I'll say it again.
你老家印度
India.
能让我住在车库吗
Can I just stay in the garage?
别这样  今晚你先睡沙发吧
Don't do that. We'll make up the couch for you
明早起来再想办法
and figure out something in the morning.
谢谢
Thank you.
来吧  我帮你铺上床单
Come on, I'll get you some sheets.
然后再测测我的血压
Then we'll see if I can beat my high score
是不是冲上新高了
on the blood pressure machine.
咱们就不该把这些熊孩子留在身边
Never should've had all these kids so close together.
你没事吧
You okay?
我睡不着
I can't sleep.
怎么了
What's wrong?
贝弗利觉得
Beverly believes
我潜意识中把我的旧房间当做一个逃生出口
I unconsciously consider my old room an escape hatch.
你在为这件事烦恼吗
Is that bothering you?
没错  我才不喜欢什么潜意识呢
Yes. I don't care for unconscious thoughts.
人家和大脑是一辈子的好朋友
My brain and I are best friends.
它什么事都会告诉我
It should tell me everything.
我是说和我们恋情的关系
I mean, how it relates to our relationship,
不是你和你大脑的兄弟浪漫史
not the bromance between you and your brain.
万一她是对的呢
What if she's correct?
就是说我俩之间有问题吗
Doesn't that say something troubling about us?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只是觉得你是喜欢安排好
I just think you're the kind of person
应急计划的人
who likes a contingency plan.
这倒是
That is true.
你知道吗
Did you know I figured out
我已经想清楚了  世界末日来临后
in which order I would eat all my friends
我会按什么顺序吃掉所有朋友
in the event of an apocalypse?
你不可以再和你的大脑整天混在一起了
You need to stop hanging out with your brain so much.
它就是个坏朋友
It's not a good influence.
如果你是想找零钱
If you're looking for spare change,
我已经扫荡干净了
I already cleaned it out.
没想到我的人生会变成这样
Didn't think this is where my life would be.
我也是
Me, either.
我有卧室你睡沙发
I'm in a bedroom and you're on a couch.
我居然是赢家
I'm actually winning.
咱俩都正走霉运
You know, we're both down on our luck.
也许我俩应该找地方一起住
Maybe you and I should try to get a place together.
听我说
Okay, listen to me.
根本没理由离开这里
There is no reason to leave here.
这里很棒  所有人都很友好
This is great. Everyone's nice.
非常舒服
It's comfortable.
如果一切按计划进行  这里就是我的养老院了
If all goes according to plan, this is my retirement home.
如果你更加独立的话
Wouldn't you feel better about yourself
不会自我感觉更好一些吗
if you were more independent?
比在他们家蒸汽淋浴里的感觉更好吗
Better than I feel in their steam shower?
我觉得不会
I don't think so.
佩妮是主菜
Penny would be the entree.
莱纳德算是奶酪盘
Then Leonard's basically a cheese course.
因为我爱你  所以你是甜点
And because I love you, you're dessert.
我也想说"好甜蜜"
I want to say "Aw,"
但我要说"好恶心"
but I'm gonna say "Ew."
不  我这样做
No, you see, I'm doing this
我就不再是被宠坏的孩子了
so I can stop being spoiled and, you know,
成长为一个成年人
grow as a person.
好样的
Good for you.
这个三明治里有价值6块钱的火腿
This sandwich has six dollars worth of ham in it.
你在朋友家吃白食  你一点点内疚感都没有吗
Don't you even feel a little bad sponging off your friends?
我上过艺术学院
Hey, look, I went to art college,
我想成为美术设计师
I tried to make it as a graphic artist,
漫画家
a comic book artist,
知道我努力得到了什么吗
and you know what I got for my efforts?
瘦骨嶙峋
A visible rib cage.
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
你可以看到我的心跳
You could see my heart beating.
无意冒犯  但我没上过艺术学院
Well, no offense, but I didn't go to art school.
我有天体物理学的博士学位
I have a PhD in astrophysics.
很好  流落街头时头上没有屋顶
Oh, great, it'll be easier for you to look up at the stars
你观星更容易
without a roof over your head.
早
Morning.
你知道拉杰昨晚搬出去了吗
Did you know Raj moved out last night?
什么  为什么
What? Why?
"莱纳德和佩妮  抱歉我带来了这么多麻烦
"Leonard and Penny, I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused.
我去霍华德家住
I went to stay at Howard's.
另外  小桂子和我在一起
P.S., Cinnamon's with me,
但如果你们想耍谢尔顿
But if you feel like messing with Sheldon,
就告诉他  小桂子在楼里走丢了"
tell him she's loose in the building."
感觉好糟糕啊
I feel terrible.
我们要接他回来吗
Should we go bring him back?
是你担心有室友
Well, you're the one worried
是我们婚姻有问题的表现
having someone live with us is a sign of problems.
那只是因为我妈让我有了这种想法
Oh, that was just because my mother got in my head.
就好像恶魔上身了  但上身的不是恶魔而是...
It's like being possessed, but instead of Satan, it's--
其实没差别啦
Actually, it's the same thing.
好的  那我们叫他回来
All right, so we'll ask him to come back.
很好
Well, great.
你不先换衣服吗
Don't you want to get dressed first?
稍等
Just one second.
救命  小桂子在楼里走丢了
Help! Cinnamon's loose in the building!
艾米  快  锁门
Amy, quick, lock the door!
如果我们让你难受真是抱歉
We're so sorry if we made you feel uncomfortable.
我们吵架真不是因为你
We really weren't fighting about you.
我只是不想成为朋友的负担
I just never want to be a burden on my friends.
我也是  不想成为负担
Me, either. Don't want to be a burden.
是孩子的声音吗  我去看看
Hey, is that the baby? I'll go check.
你不是负担
You are not a burden,
我们希望你回来一起住
and we want you to come back and stay with us.
但我让谢尔顿不高兴
But I also upset Sheldon,
如果我住在那里  他不会去你们家的
and he's not gonna want to come over if I'm there.
这是你更应该来住的原因
More reasons for you to stay.
哈雷没事
Halley's fine.
你知道她在我父母家呢吧
You know she's at my parents' house, right?
她正享受着人生中最美好的时光
And she's having the time of her life.
如果你想改变一下
If you ever want to change things up,
我家随时欢迎你
you're always welcome here.
别来我们卧室就成  白痴
Just not in our bedroom, you dumbass.
非常感谢  但我想
I appreciate it, but I think
住莱纳德和佩妮家  对大家都更有利
staying with Leonard and Penny makes more sense for everyone.
-就这么定了  -告诉你一声
- Then it's settled. - And just so you know,
这只是暂时的
it's only temporary.
我不会太给方便就随便的
I'm not gonna get too comfortable.
很好
Good.
谁家都不想要一个吃一辈子白食的
Nobody needs a mooch living in their house forever.
这样说你家宝宝可不好
Hey, that's no way to talk about your baby.
知道吗  我为我们感到骄傲
You know what? I'm proud of us.
佩妮和莱纳德收留了拉杰
Yeah, with Penny and Leonard taking in Raj,
斯图尔特住在霍华德和伯纳黛特家
and Stuart living with Howard and Bernadette,
我们是这个小团队中唯一一对
we're the only couple of our social group
不需要用第三者
who doesn't need to fill the holes
填补关系中大坑的人
in their relationship with a third party.
对  我们完胜
Yup, we're killin' it.